Guide to the John Howard Griffin Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XXI. Photographs
  - Pierre Reverdy Born September 11, 1889, in Narbonne, France; died June 17, 1960. His early poems, Les Epaves du ciel, in 1924, surrealists hailed Reverdy as the greatest living poet. A collection of Reverdy's poetry. Main d'ouvre, was published in 1949, and his poetic theories are explained in his Le Gant de crin, published in 1926. Solesmes, France, 1946, (1 photograph) (Box 37, Folder 950)
  - Rhein archivist, Rhein, France, 3 November 1961, (1 photograph) (Box 37, Folder 951)
  - Scenery, [n.p.], [1966], (1 photograph) (Box 37, Folder 952)
  - Don Shoemaker Snapshot with dog, Santa Maria, Morelia, Mexico, September 1965, (1 photograph) (Box 37, Folder 953)
  - Saint Barthelemy's Church, Liege, 1964, (2 photographs) (Box 37, Folder 954)
  - Taos Pueblo, N.M., 1964, (2 photographs) (Box 37, Folder 955)
  - Father James Thompson Portraits and snapshots, [v.p.], 1963-1975, (5 photographs) (Box 37, Folder 956)
  - Father James Thompson's church and environment, Ferriday, LA, 1963, (4 photographs) (Box 37, Folder 957)
  - Two nuns (one of Griffin's favorite photographs), [Mexico], 27 July 1963, (1 photograph) (Box 37, Folder 958)
- Series XXII: Photographs by Others
  - Gregory Griffin Photograph of prairie dog, Fort Worth, texas, 18 July 1962, (1 photograph) (Box 37, Folder 959)
  - Gregory Griffin Photograph of harpy eagle, Fort Worth, texas, 18 July 1962, (1 photograph) (Box 37, Folder 960)
  - Father G. Curtsinger Sea shore, [n.p.], [1967], (1 photograph) (Box 37, Folder 961)
  - Father George Trees, [n.p.], [1967], (3 photographs) (Box 37, Folder 962)
  - Joel Orent Photographs of two men, [n.p.], 1975, (2 photographs) (Box 37, Folder 963)
  - Ron Sugiyama Girl playing, [n.p.], 1972, (1 photograph) (Box 37, Folder 964)
  - Thomas Merton Rocks and water can, [n.p.], 1967, (2 photographs) (Box 37, Folder 965)